Guide to the John B. Bender Papers
Stanford University. Libraries.
- Additional Papers, Accession ARCH-2005-088
  - Publication Files, Subseries 5
    - Responses to Imagining the Penitentiary, 1987 (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - University of Chicago Press contracts (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Times Literary Supplement, correspondence, 1976-1993 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - The Ends of Rhetoric - contract, correspondence, 1988-1995 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Blake's "Infant Sorrow" article – correspondence and illustrations, 1981-1983 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Blake's "Infant Sorrow" article - drafts and notes (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Blake's "Infant Sorrow" article - sources (Box 12, Folder 8)
    - Regimes of Description, uncorrected proof (pp. 1-117) (Box 12, Folder 9)
    - Regimes of Description, uncorrected proof (pp. 118-end) (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - "The Novel as Modern Myth" (article for Merker), 2004 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - "Hume's Learned and Conversible World" - drafts and correspondence, 2002 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - "Hume's Learned and Conversible World" - drafts and correspondence, 2000-2001 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Imaging the Penitentiary - reviews and notices, 1987-1988 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Imaging the Penitentiary - correspondence, 1990-1995 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Imaging the Penitentiary - correspondence, 1986-1989 (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Imaging the Penitentiary – letters re complementary copies (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Restricted Files, Subseries 6
    - Recommendations for students and colleagues: general files, 1969-1993 (Box 14)
    - Recommendations for students and colleagues: by name A-Y, 1980-1999 (Box 14)
    - Recommendations for students A-L, 1979-2000 (Box 15)
      (Some files re Ph.D. oral exams; some contain student's papers, research proposals, etc.)
    - Recommendations for students M-Z, 1973-1999 (Box 16)
    - Recommendations for colleagues: attendees from Mellon and NEH seminars, 1980-1995 (Box 17)
    - Recommendations for colleagues: in general, 1972-1995 (Box 17)
    - Miscellaneous folders of recommendations (Box 17)
    - Unsorted recommendations (Box 17)
    - Unsorted recommendations (Box 18)
    - Two student theses, 1997-1998 (Box 18)
- Additional papers, Accession ARCH-2006-184
  - Correspondence re: Pictures and Permissions, 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Photography - Orders, Receipts, Invoices, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Michael Fried, articles by and Bender's notes on, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Tom Jones Introduction - Final Text and Working Materials, 1994-1995 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Exemplarity and Excess in Fielding's Fiction [resource articles] (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Tom Jones, Oxford University Press, contract and correspondence, 1991-1995 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Prison Project [Imagining the Penitentiary] - Pictures and Buildings (other than Piranesi) (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Prison Book Illustrations - Permissions (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Prison Project - Museum Work, New York (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Prison Book Illustrations - Research Assistance, Correspondence, Lists, 1981-1986 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Clark Library, UCLA - Ordering Nature in the Enlightenment Conference, 1998 May (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - "The Novel and the Enlightenment" NSECS – OCTAV (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - "Enlightenment Science, Fictionality, and the Novel" Berlin, 1994 Sep (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Miscellaneous materials pertaining to research on various topics (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Hogarth Essay Materials, 1998 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - "Fiction and Enlightenment," Representations 61 - Proofs and correspondence, 1997 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - American Society for 18th Century Studies, meeting held at San Francisco and Stanford, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - MLA, 1973 Dec (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Masque Seminar, MLA 1973, and correspondence with David M. Bergeron (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Northern California Renaissance Conference, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 11)